[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which city hosts the International Clown Hall of Fame?", "correct_answer": "West Allis, Wisconsin", "incorrect_answers": ["West Hollywood, CA", "Saratoga, NY", "Sarasota, Florida"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The pH of solids in solid form can be measured using indicator paper.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the figurative expression a white elephant?", "correct_answer": "A pricey and useless possession", "incorrect_answers": ["Something that is idolized but that does not exist", "An extraordinary person", "A chimera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What bacterium is believed to be the smallest living organism that is capable to grow and reproduce independently?", "correct_answer": "Mycoplasma genitalium", "incorrect_answers": ["Staphylococcus aureus", "Escherichia coli", "Carsonella ruddii"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first human birth through embryo transfer was announced on February 3, 1984. Who was in charge of the research team that carried out the project?", "correct_answer": "Dr. John Buster", "incorrect_answers": ["Dr. Emily Richardson", "Dr. Elliot Smith", "Dr. Benjamin Lewis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors was not included in the voice cast of the 2003 animated blockbuster movie Finding Nemo?", "correct_answer": "Renee Zellweger", "incorrect_answers": ["Geoffrey Rush", "Ellen DeGeneres", "Willem Dafoe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1728, he became the first person to sail into the Arctic Ocean and proved that Asia and North America are not joined by land.", "correct_answer": "Bering", "incorrect_answers": ["Cook", "Scott", "Peary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the word albedo, which comes from Latin?", "correct_answer": "A value for the reflectivity of an object", "incorrect_answers": ["A bright region on the suns chromosphere", "A disease afflicting canines in which the fur around the tail falls out", "An adjustment to a projectiles flight using retro-rockets"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the names of the two space shuttles sent to destroy the meteor that is spelling certain doom in the film Armageddon?", "correct_answer": "The Freedom and the Independence", "incorrect_answers": ["The Columbus and the Destiny", "The United and the Free", "The Hope and the Pride"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This African desert, famous for its enormous sand dunes, is considered the oldest desert in the world, having endured its current arid conditions for at least 80 million years.", "correct_answer": "Namib Desert", "incorrect_answers": ["Libyan Desert", "Kalahari Desert", "Kara Kum Desert"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1976 movie Carrie was based on a 1952 movie of the same name starring Laurence Olivier.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many teeth does and adult have?", "correct_answer": "32", "incorrect_answers": ["28", "30", "26"]}]